[{"filename": "1.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 296, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44082853", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 215, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "1.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 62, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 87, "end_line": 109, "parameters": [], "filename": "1.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "10.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 295, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44059829", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 6, "macro_count": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 27, "name": "MIN", "long_name": "MIN( long long int a , long long int b)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "10.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 27, "name": "MAX", "long_name": "MAX( long long int a , long long int b)", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 57, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "10.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 23, "name": "MOD", "long_name": "MOD( long long int x)", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "10.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 192, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 139, "parameters": [], "filename": "10.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "100.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 192, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43748906", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 181, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 10, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "100.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 34, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "101.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 147, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43748161", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 138, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 27, "parameters": [], "filename": "101.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "102.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 135, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43747509", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 117, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "102.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "103.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 229, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43747158", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 210, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "103.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "104.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 154, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43745230", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 147, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "104.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "105.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 255, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43744732", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 252, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "105.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "106.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 194, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43744155", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 191, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 25, "parameters": [], "filename": "106.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "107.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 152, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43743655", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 141, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "107.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "108.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 185, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43740908", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 178, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "108.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "109.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 205, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43738539", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 196, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "109.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "11.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 167, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44056232", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 145, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "11.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "110.cpp", "nloc": 56, "token_count": 332, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43737009", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 13, "macro_count": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 65, "name": "fast_exp", "long_name": "fast_exp( llp base , llp exp , llp m)", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 81, "parameters": ["base", "exp", "m"], "filename": "110.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 178, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 205, "end_line": 261, "parameters": [], "filename": "110.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "111.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 287, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43736436", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 276, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "111.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 83, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "112.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 190, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43736298", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 10, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 172, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "112.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "113.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 209, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43732651", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 202, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "113.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "114.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 178, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43732127", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 171, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "114.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "115.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 247, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43729344", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 37, "name": "count", "long_name": "count( ll n)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 63, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "115.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 191, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 121, "parameters": [], "filename": "115.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "116.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 191, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43727424", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 177, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "116.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "117.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 158, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43723838", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 151, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "117.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 26, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "118.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 209, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43723340", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 198, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "118.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "119.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 231, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43722164", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 218, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "119.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "12.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 155, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44052493", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "macro_count": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 146, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "12.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "120.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 194, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43719839", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 181, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "120.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "121.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 187, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43717707", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 174, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "121.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "122.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 176, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43716368", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 158, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "122.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "123.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 198, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43715749", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 23, "name": "max", "long_name": "max( double a , double b)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 17, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "123.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 167, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "123.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "124.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 361, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43713128", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 42, "token_count": 354, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "124.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 91, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "125.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 201, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43712509", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 194, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "125.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "126.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 213, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43704864", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 206, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "126.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "127.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 198, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43704712", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 191, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "127.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "128.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 532, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43704266", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 20, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 514, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "128.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 89, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "129.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 179, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43702784", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 172, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "129.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "13.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 174, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44047855", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 165, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "13.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "130.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 219, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43702243", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 206, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "130.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "131.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 201, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43702135", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 190, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "131.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "132.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 191, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43701764", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 182, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "132.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "133.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 252, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43698761", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 245, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "133.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "134.cpp", "nloc": 67, "token_count": 544, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43694209", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 16, "nloc": 61, "token_count": 516, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 207, "parameters": [], "filename": "134.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 151, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "135.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 176, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43693080", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 151, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "136.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 191, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43692673", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 178, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 8, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "136.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 26, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "137.cpp", "nloc": 16, "token_count": 148, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43690308", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 132, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "137.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "138.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 271, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43687741", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 260, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "138.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "14.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 171, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44044838", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 164, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "14.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "15.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 198, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44043904", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 191, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "15.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "16.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 210, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44041144", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 185, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "16.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "17.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 195, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44038547", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 181, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "17.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "18.cpp", "nloc": 56, "token_count": 335, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44036287", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 53, "token_count": 326, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "18.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 111, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "19.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 308, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44032820", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "macro_count": 18, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 39, "token_count": 299, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 147, "parameters": [], "filename": "19.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 91, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 200, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44079851", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 191, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "2.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "20.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 223, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44031970", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 216, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "20.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "21.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 185, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44031362", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 158, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 28, "parameters": [], "filename": "21.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 18, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "22.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 294, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44030767", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "17100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 224, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 145, "parameters": [], "filename": "22.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 105, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "23.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 144, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44028796", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 121, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "23.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "24.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 147, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44025405", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 138, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "24.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "25.cpp", "nloc": 15, "token_count": 136, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44020892", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 116, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "25.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "26.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 159, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44017535", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 148, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "26.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "27.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 249, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44013872", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 246, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "27.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "28.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 199, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44010524", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 192, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 36, "parameters": [], "filename": "28.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 34, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "29.cpp", "nloc": 108, "token_count": 405, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44009168", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 76, "macro_count": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 79, "name": "valid", "long_name": "valid( double x)", "start_line": 132, "end_line": 141, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "29.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 113, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 144, "end_line": 169, "parameters": [], "filename": "29.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 26, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 179, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44079713", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 170, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "3.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "30.cpp", "nloc": 63, "token_count": 399, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44007113", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 10, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 62, "name": "multiply", "long_name": "multiply( ll num1 , ll num2 , ll mod)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["num1", "num2", "mod"], "filename": "30.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 66, "name": "powmod2", "long_name": "powmod2( ll base , ll exponent , ll mod)", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 73, "parameters": ["base", "exponent", "mod"], "filename": "30.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 62, "name": "powmod", "long_name": "powmod( ll base , ll exponent , ll mod)", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 97, "parameters": ["base", "exponent", "mod"], "filename": "30.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 30, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 99, "end_line": 105, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "30.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 144, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 109, "end_line": 145, "parameters": [], "filename": "30.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "31.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 158, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44005374", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 151, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 20, "parameters": [], "filename": "31.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 16, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "32.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 175, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43998983", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 168, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 20, "parameters": [], "filename": "32.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "33.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 187, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43995830", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 155, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "33.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "34.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 236, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43995381", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 229, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "34.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "35.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 166, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43993354", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "macro_count": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 157, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "35.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "36.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 395, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43990896", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 44, "token_count": 386, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "36.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 109, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "37.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 215, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43988456", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 208, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 34, "parameters": [], "filename": "37.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "38.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 348, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43978719", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 48, "token_count": 341, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "38.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 109, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "39.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 167, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43975470", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 160, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "39.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "4.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 208, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44078255", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 197, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "4.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "40.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 249, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43951618", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 216, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "40.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "41.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 171, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43941432", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 134, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "41.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "42.cpp", "nloc": 57, "token_count": 296, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43941086", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 118, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( double d)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 55, "parameters": ["d"], "filename": "42.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 84, "name": "bin", "long_name": "bin( int l)", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 105, "parameters": ["l"], "filename": "42.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 74, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 109, "end_line": 147, "parameters": [], "filename": "42.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "43.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 178, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43939859", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "4400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 157, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 28, "parameters": [], "filename": "43.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 20, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "44.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 300, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43938391", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 38, "token_count": 289, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "44.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 77, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "45.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 299, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43937192", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 44, "token_count": 292, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "45.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 95, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "46.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 299, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43937173", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 44, "token_count": 292, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "46.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 91, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "47.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 194, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43933573", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 187, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "47.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "48.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 167, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43930130", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 160, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "48.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "49.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 187, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43920026", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 167, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "49.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "5.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 289, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44075933", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 229, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "5.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 34, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "5.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "50.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 196, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43918626", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 189, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "50.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "51.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 223, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43917923", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 16, "macro_count": 22, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 167, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 157, "parameters": [], "filename": "51.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "52.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 250, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43917722", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 16, "macro_count": 22, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 194, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 163, "parameters": [], "filename": "52.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "53.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 183, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43910295", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 172, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "53.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "54.cpp", "nloc": 15, "token_count": 134, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43899596", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 127, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "54.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "55.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 229, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43890344", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 194, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "55.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "56.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 157, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43889260", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 144, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char const * argv [ ])", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "56.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "57.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 208, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43886821", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 9, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 171, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "57.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "58.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 212, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43886773", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 11, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 171, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "58.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "59.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 148, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43885448", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 133, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "59.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "6.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 180, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44072805", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 173, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "6.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "60.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 213, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43876887", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 204, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 56, "parameters": [], "filename": "60.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 48, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "61.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 213, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43876875", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 204, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "61.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 95, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "62.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 194, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43876831", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 181, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "62.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "63.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 181, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43876513", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 174, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 27, "parameters": [], "filename": "63.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "64.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 205, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43876280", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 7, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 94, "name": "buscar_max", "long_name": "buscar_max( double lamparas [ ] , int n , int l , double maximo)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 21, "parameters": ["]", "n", "l", "maximo"], "filename": "64.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 91, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 24, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "64.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "65.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 205, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43876220", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 7, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 94, "name": "buscar_max", "long_name": "buscar_max( double lamparas [ ] , int n , int l , double maximo)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 21, "parameters": ["]", "n", "l", "maximo"], "filename": "65.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 91, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 24, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "65.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "66.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 196, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43875702", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 189, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 38, "parameters": [], "filename": "66.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "67.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 159, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43874372", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 150, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 26, "parameters": [], "filename": "67.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "68.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 256, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43874039", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 244, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "68.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 38, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "69.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 157, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43873790", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 146, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 8, "end_line": 23, "parameters": [], "filename": "69.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 16, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "7.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 168, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44068754", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 161, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "7.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "70.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 269, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43872779", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 220, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "70.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 79, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "71.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 214, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43870911", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 207, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 60, "parameters": [], "filename": "71.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 56, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "72.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 160, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43868946", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 149, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "72.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "73.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 156, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43868070", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 145, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "73.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "74.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 212, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43863595", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 194, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "74.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "75.cpp", "nloc": 54, "token_count": 357, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43863172", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 27, "name": "abs", "long_name": "abs( int n)", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 11, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "75.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 322, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "75.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "76.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 159, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43831365", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 148, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 22, "parameters": [], "filename": "76.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "77.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 330, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43824277", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 46, "name": "split", "long_name": "split( string strToSplit , char delimeter)", "start_line": 8, "end_line": 15, "parameters": ["strToSplit", "delimeter"], "filename": "77.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 262, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 18, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "77.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 46, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "78.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 205, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43822560", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 180, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "78.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "79.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 278, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43818475", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 271, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "79.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "8.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 224, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44067761", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 217, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "8.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "80.cpp", "nloc": 120, "token_count": 701, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43817878", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 4, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 39, "token_count": 228, "name": "merge", "long_name": "merge( int arr [ ] , int l , int m , int r)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 59, "parameters": ["]", "l", "m", "r"], "filename": "80.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 67, "name": "mergeSort", "long_name": "mergeSort( int arr [ ] , int l , int r)", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 75, "parameters": ["]", "l", "r"], "filename": "80.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 67, "token_count": 391, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 190, "parameters": [], "filename": "80.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 114, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "81.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 278, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43816392", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 130, "name": "chk", "long_name": "chk( int total , double mid , int a [ ] , int len)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["total", "mid", "]", "len"], "filename": "81.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 140, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "81.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "82.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 284, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43816292", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 132, "name": "chk", "long_name": "chk( int total , double mid , int a [ ] , int len)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["total", "mid", "]", "len"], "filename": "82.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 144, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "82.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "83.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 296, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43816210", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 136, "name": "chk", "long_name": "chk( int total , double mid , int a [ ] , int len)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["total", "mid", "]", "len"], "filename": "83.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 144, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "83.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "84.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 202, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43814671", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 195, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 26, "parameters": [], "filename": "84.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "85.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 397, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43811973", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 49, "token_count": 390, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "85.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "86.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 397, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43811963", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 49, "token_count": 390, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "86.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 101, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "87.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 397, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43811915", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 49, "token_count": 390, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "87.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 101, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "88.cpp", "nloc": 57, "token_count": 396, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43809604", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 10, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 31, "name": "dcmp", "long_name": "dcmp( double x , double y)", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "88.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 269, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 149, "parameters": [], "filename": "88.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 85, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "89.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 192, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43806918", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 185, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "89.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "90.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 182, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43804717", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 175, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "90.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "91.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 219, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43803822", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 38, "token_count": 210, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "91.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 89, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "92.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 341, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43794800", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 43, "token_count": 332, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 119, "parameters": [], "filename": "92.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 109, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "93.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 181, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43791128", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 168, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "93.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "94.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 278, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43789857", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 271, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "94.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "95.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 152, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43787215", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 126, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "95.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "96.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 261, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43786392", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 17, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 222, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 125, "parameters": [], "filename": "96.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 85, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "97.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 200, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43780858", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 191, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "97.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "98.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 204, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43780546", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 193, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "98.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "99.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 203, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43749721", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 192, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 32, "parameters": [], "filename": "99.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 26, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]}
]